[
  {
    "id": "T1A01",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "Which of the following is part of the Basis and Purpose of the Amateur Radio Service?",
    "answers": [
      "Providing personal radio communications for as many citizens as possible",
      "Providing communications for international non-profit organizations",
      "Advancing skills in the technical and communication phases of the radio art",
      "All these choices are correct"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T1A02",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "Which agency regulates and enforces the rules for the Amateur Radio Service in the United States?",
    "answers": [
      "FEMA",
      "Homeland Security",
      "The FCC",
      "All these choices are correct"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T1A03",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "What do the FCC rules state regarding the use of a phonetic alphabet for station identification in the Amateur Radio Service?",
    "answers": [
      "It is required when transmitting emergency messages",
      "It is encouraged",
      "It is required when in contact with foreign stations",
      "All these choices are correct"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T1A04",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "How many operator/primary station license grants may be held by any one person?",
    "answers": [
      "One",
      "No more than two",
      "One for each band on which the person plans to operate",
      "One for each permanent station location from which the person plans to operate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T1A05",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "What proves that the FCC has issued an operator/primary license grant?",
    "answers": [
      "A printed copy of the certificate of successful completion of examination",
      "An email notification from the NCVEC granting the license",
      "The license appears in the FCC ULS database",
      "All these choices are correct"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T1A06",
    "correct": 3,
    "question": "What is the FCC Part 97 definition of a beacon?",
    "answers": [
      "A government transmitter marking the amateur radio band edges",
      "A bulletin sent by the FCC to announce a national emergency",
      "A continuous transmission of weather information authorized in the amateur bands by the National Weather Service",
      "An amateur station transmitting communications for the purposes of observing propagation or related experimental activities"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T1A07",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "What is the FCC Part 97 definition of a space station?",
    "answers": [
      "Any satellite orbiting Earth",
      "A manned satellite orbiting Earth",
      "An amateur station located more than 50 km above Earth's surface",
      "An amateur station using amateur radio satellites for relay of signals"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T1A08",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "Which of the following entities recommends transmit/receive channels and other parameters for auxiliary and repeater stations?",
    "answers": [
      "Frequency Spectrum Manager appointed by the FCC",
      "Volunteer Frequency Coordinator recognized by local amateurs",
      "FCC Regional Field Office",
      "International Telecommunication Union"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T1A09",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "Who selects a Frequency Coordinator?",
    "answers": [
      "The FCC Office of Spectrum Management and Coordination Policy",
      "The local chapter of the Office of National Council of Independent Frequency Coordinators",
      "Amateur operators in a local or regional area whose stations are eligible to be repeater or auxiliary stations",
      "FCC Regional Field Office"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T1A10",
    "correct": 3,
    "question": "What is the Radio Amateur Civil Emergency Service (RACES)?",
    "answers": [
      "A radio service using amateur frequencies for emergency management or civil defense communications",
      "A radio service using amateur stations for emergency management or civil defense communications",
      "An emergency service using amateur operators certified by a civil defense organization as being enrolled in that organization",
      "All these choices are correct"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T1A11",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "When is willful interference to other amateur radio stations permitted?",
    "answers": [
      "To stop another amateur station that is breaking the FCC rules",
      "At no time",
      "When making short test transmissions",
      "At any time, stations in the Amateur Radio Service are not protected from willful interference"
    ]
  }
]